Emanuel Torres Clemente

Frontend Developer

Villa de Cura, Venezuela (GMT-4) (+58) 424 335 9570 emanueljtc@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/emanuel-torres-clemente / http://emanueljtc.github.io/

Frontend developer with more than 6 years of experience creating and supporting different information systems, web pages and mobile applications with JS and CSS. At the same time, he worked with Frameworks such as React, Tailwind, SASS or LEES for the Front-End. Passionate about technology and continuous self-learning, I seek to improve my technical and soft skills. I am looking for an opportunity where I can contribute to the development of new projects that help me take on new challenges and improve my skills as a Frontend developer.

EXPERIENCE

Pepper— November, 2021 - December, 2023 — Developer Frontend

- Improve the flow of old modules of the operational information system by 90%.
- Implement 100% new modules within the operational information system.
- Implement new flows within the company's sales and transportation mobile applications, further helping their processes.

Stack tecnológico: React, Tailwind, Typescript, React Native, Jest.

Ticxel — March, 2021 - November, 2021 — Frontend Developer

• Preparation of 100% of each of the modules of the website of a home sales agency in the USA. The website helped the agency in the percentage of sales.

Stack tecnológico: React, Typescript, CSS.

Total Web Development— May, 2019 - March, 2021 — Frontend Developer

• Development of 100% of each of the modules of different web pages, mobile applications and information systems. Each of the modules and functionalities developed contributed growth in each of the areas for which each project was intended.

Technological stack: React, CSS, SASS.

Jida Developments— November, 2018 - February, 2019 — Frontend Developer

Contribute changes to 50% of the modules of the mobile application for the Argentine soccer league. My work
contributed to growth in the internal information of the soccer league.

Technological stack: Beyond JS, LESS, Polymer.

Hispano Soluciones C.A— January, 2018 - November, 2018 — Frontend Developer

 Work on the development of each of the modules of different web pages and information systems for different clients of the company. These contributions boosted the agility of internal processes and improved many other aspects of the agents involved with each project, such as increased sales. Technology stack: React, HTML, CSS, SASS

Kimberly Clark C.A — July, 2017 - January, 2018 — Frontend Developer

• I helped create modules that gave significant contributions to the sales and production area of the company. Technological stack: HTML, CSS, SASS.

SKILLS

Stack: JS, React Js, React Native, CSS, Tailwind, SASS, LESS, JEST.

Languages: English, Spanish

EDUCATION

Rómulo Gallegos Experimental University – San Juan de los Morros, Venezuela. Computer Engineering, May 2017.